yourbiggestagetell.com 2018-11-13

# None

Thank you for visiting the Beverly Hills MD website (the "Site"). Please review the this Privacy Policy (the "Policy" or "Policies") carefully. We value the importance of your trust and therefore have set forth these policies to better explain how Beverly Hills MD, LLC. (collectively, "Beverly Hills MD, LLC.", "Us", "We", or "Our") collect, protect, and use your information. The information that we collect may be used as part by us including but not limited to, our Company websites, web pages, advertisements, social media, and the Site. 

By using the Site you irrevocably accept these Policies. If you do not agree with the Policies address herein, then you do not have the right to access, view, download, purchase products, or use the Site and therefore, should not do so. 

_________________________________________________________________________________________________

\- DATA AND HOW IT'S USED -

Automatically Collected Data: To better enhance your browsing experience of the Site, we passively and automatically collect data, such as site usage information and IP information ("Usage Data"). The Usage Data collected identifies how the Site is accessed and used throughout, including the type of browser used, operating system, type of device used, time of browser, page views, and the use of features and services found on the Site. This arithmetical data allows us to understand and identify what the user finds both interesting and relevant to better tailor the content provided. 

We also automatically collect the IP address or other unique classifying information from the computer or other device used to access the Site. We may use the information collected to help understand user trends, track user's movement throughout the Site, and to help identify any issues with our servers. 

How the Data is Used and Shared: Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we may share non-personal information, such as Usage data, as stated herein. We will not provide any personal information to third parties without prior consent from you. 

The information we collect may used for the following, including (i) to verify who you are, the User (ii) to fulfill your purchases made on the Site, (iii) to provide complete access to the features available on the Site, (iv) to respond to any inquiries, (v) to assist and communicate information on your purchases, (vi) Improving the Users experience.

*Legal Disclosure: Under certain circumstances and as it may be required by law, we may disclose and transfer information, including your personal information, the usage data, and IP information. We may disclose this information for the following reasons including, a mandated legal obligation, request from governmental authorities, or to protect rights, safety, and security the public. 

Cookies: To better serve the user and to (i) facilitate site navigation and (ii) personalize your experience, including but not limited tailoring advertisements we use Cookies. Cookies are data files placed on your computer or other device when it is used to visit the Site. If you prefer to not accept cookies, you may change your browser setting. Your settings can be adjusted to notify when you receive cookies, which you may choose to accept or reject. Please note that enabling a cookie blocker may alter or restrict certain features or services available on the Site.

Third Party Cookies: This Site uses remarketing services such as Google Analytics Advertising Features and Google Ad Words. These services collect data pertaining to your past visits to this Site and use cookies to collectively present advertisements tailored to your interest ("Remarketed Ads"). These Remarketed Ads may appear on certain third party websites, including but not limited to, Google search results page, websites within the Google Display Network, or any other third party vendor network. If you prefer not to receive Remarketed Ads, you can set your preferences [HERE](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) or you can OPT-OUT of all Remarketed Ads by visiting [OPT-OUT](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

Email Addresses: We will never sell any of your personal information. We could share your email with third parties to perform services on your behalf.

Data You May Provide: We may collect personal information, such as your name, email, telephone number, home address, and payment information. This information is used to identify you as an individual. This information may be collect at the time of purchase or by opt-in from any of our registration forms found on the Site. The type of information we collect depends on your use of the Site. We may ask you to provide more information, such as opinions or statements relating to the product. 

\- HOW TO OPT-OUT - 

If you do not wish to receive our newsletters, product promotions, or any related advertisement material, you can opt-out. You can opt out by visiting the "Manage Subscriptions" tab at the bottom of your email. Your request will be processed in (5) five business days. Please be advised that this will not deter advertisement while you browser the Site or the Internet. 

\- SECURITY - 

We value your security concerns and appreciate the importance of your trust. We strive to maintain reasonable safeguards to protect user's Personal Information against loss, unauthorized use and or disclosure or Personal information, and when transferring information when processing your order. 

All orders are processed through Network Merchants, LLC. The personally identifiable information Network Merchants, LLC acquires in processing payment transactions varies according to the nature of the transaction and the way in which merchants or financial institutions are using their payment services. It may include, for example, the amount of the transaction, the consumer's name, credit card number and expiration date, checking account number, billing address, and shipping address

Network Merchants, LLC uses the information collected to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to process payment transactions, to facilitate billing, and otherwise deliver the payment gateway services. Personally identifiable consumer information is used to process payment transactions and for no other purpose.

Network Merchants, LLC stores transaction information on secure computers located in a locked data center. Only a small number of employees involved in the management of the data center have physical access to these computers. Where possible, Network Merchants, LLC encrypts information stored on their computers as a further measure of protection. Network Merchants, LLC uses state-of-the-art firewalls and other security technology to prevent their computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons. Information security is critical to our business. Nevertheless, nothing can be 100% secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

\- YOUR CONSENT TO PROCESS INFORMATION -

This Site, and any webpage associated with Beverly Hills MD, LLC. are operated in and governed by, and in accordance with, the laws of the United States. This Site is intended for the use of residents of the United States. Please note that information we collect may be transferred and processed in the United States, therefore be aware if you are located in Canada, the European Union, or any other country outside the United States. By using the Site or by providing us with any information you irrevocably agree and acknowledge that (i) the Site is subject to the laws of the United States and (ii) the collection, processing, maintenance, and transfer of such information in done in the United States in which the laws on privacy may not be as comprehensive to those in the country where you, the User, reside and/or are a citizen of, and (iii) you waive any claims that may arise under those laws. 

\- COMMUNICATIONS -

You acknowledge that telephone calls to or from Beverly Hills MD are monitored and recorded and you agree to such monitoring and recording.

You verify that any contact information provided to Beverly Hills MD, including, but not limited to, your mailing address, shipping address, e-mail address, residential phone number, and mobile phone number is true and accurate. You further verify that you are the telephone subscriber and/or that you own any telephone numbers that you provide to Beverly Hills MD. You acknowledge that by voluntarily providing your telephone numbers to Beverly Hills MD, you expressly agree to be contacted at the telephone numbers you provide.

You consent to receive e-mails, pre-recorded voice messages and/or autodialed calls (including text messages) by or on behalf of Beverly Hills MD relating to this Agreement, any purchase or transaction with Beverly Hills MD, matters related to your account (including debt collection), and promotions regarding Beverly Hills MD products. These communications may be made by or on behalf of Beverly Hills MD, even if your phone number is registered on any state or federal Do Not Call list. You acknowledge that you may incur a charge for these calls by your telephone carrier and that Beverly Hills MD will not be responsible for these charges.

Beverly Hills MD may obtain, and you expressly agree to be contacted at, e-mail addresses, mailing or shipping addresses and phone numbers provided by you directly or obtained through other lawful means, such as skip tracing. You agree to provide Beverly Hills MD notice within 30 days of any change to your contact information by writing to 

Attention: Beverly Hills MD Customer Service  
436 N Bedford Dr. STE 308  
Beverly Hills, CA 90210

or emailing customersupport@beverlyhillsmd.com.

Your consent to this communications provision is not required to make any purchase with Beverly Hills MD.

\- NOTICE TO CHANGE OF POLICY - 

Please note that we may change the information on this Privacy Policy at any time, without notice. Be advised that all changes will be effective immediately. It is recommended that you visit this page from time to time to receive the latest information on our privacy practices. 

\- HOW TO CONTACT US - 

Do you have a question or concern? We're here to help you in any way that we can. Feel free to give us a call or e-mail us. Giving you an extraordinary experience is first and foremost in everything we do.

To reach us by phone:  
1-877-828-5528

customersupport@beverlyhillsmd.com

Beverly Hills MD  
8383 Wilshire Blvd #800  
Beverly Hills, CA 90211
